{"data":[{"question":"There are six pencils ________ the box.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","d":"into","answer":"1","explain":"- In\u00a0(preposition): within an object or space","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Where is your mother? She's ________ the kitchen.","a":"in","b":"on","c":"into","d":"at","answer":"1","explain":"\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on \n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk... \n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry... \n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page... \n- Into: to the inside or inner part of a container, place, area etc.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"How many pictures are there ________ the wall?","a":"in","b":"on","c":"into","d":"at","answer":"2","explain":"\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on \n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk... \n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry... \n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page... \n- Into: to the inside or inner part of a container, place, area etc.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Are you ________ Vietnam? Yes, I am.","a":"to","b":"on","c":"into","d":"from","answer":"4","explain":"\n- From: used for stating someone's origin","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"I'm cleaning the floor. Can your help ________?","a":"I","b":"me","c":"my","d":"mine","answer":"2","explain":"- To help somebody( the object)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"What are you doing? - ________ are planting some trees.","a":"we","b":"us","c":"our","d":"ours","answer":"1","explain":"\n- We (pronoun): as the subject\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Mary is doing her homework and ________ brother is helping her.","a":"she","b":"hers","c":"her","d":"she's","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Her brother = Mary's brother","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Jane's books are on the floor. Please, put ________ on the table.","a":"they","b":"them","c":"their","d":"theirs","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Put them (object ) = put Jane's books","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"Please put this pencil in the box. I'm putting ________ in the box.","a":"it","b":"its","c":"them","d":"they","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Put it (object) = put this pencil","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"},{"question":"When's ________ birthday?","a":"his","b":"he","c":"him","d":"he's","answer":"1","explain":"- \u00a0His: a possessive determiner of he","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"3","type":"1"}]}